[
    {
        "question": "縁談",
        "answer": "えんだん"
    },
    {
        "question": "盛大",
        "answer": "せいだい"
    },
    {
        "question": "禅",
        "answer": "ぜん"
    },
    {
        "question": "如何しても",
        "answer": "どうしても"
    },
    {
        "question": "叶える",
        "answer": "かなえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "頻りに",
        "answer": "しきりに"
    },
    {
        "question": "過密",
        "answer": "かみつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "融通",
        "answer": "ゆうずう"
    },
    {
        "question": "貴族",
        "answer": "きぞく"
    },
    {
        "question": "従って",
        "answer": "したがって"
    },
    {
        "question": "巧み",
        "answer": "たくみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "排水",
        "answer": "はいすい"
    },
    {
        "question": "卯",
        "answer": "ぼう"
    },
    {
        "question": "脂肪",
        "answer": "しぼう"
    },
    {
        "question": "貧乏",
        "answer": "びんぼう"
    },
    {
        "question": "孤立",
        "answer": "こりつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "軸",
        "answer": "じく"
    },
    {
        "question": "誘惑",
        "answer": "ゆうわく"
    },
    {
        "question": "振興",
        "answer": "しんこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "水源",
        "answer": "すいげん"
    },
    {
        "question": "尽きる",
        "answer": "つきる"
    },
    {
        "question": "弾力",
        "answer": "だんりょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "即する",
        "answer": "そくする"
    },
    {
        "question": "衝撃",
        "answer": "しょうげき"
    },
    {
        "question": "適応",
        "answer": "てきおう"
    },
    {
        "question": "脱退",
        "answer": "だったい"
    },
    {
        "question": "継ぐ",
        "answer": "つぐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "甚だ",
        "answer": "はなはだ"
    },
    {
        "question": "沿岸",
        "answer": "えんがん"
    },
    {
        "question": "侍",
        "answer": "さむらい"
    },
    {
        "question": "隔たる",
        "answer": "へだたる"
    },
    {
        "question": "冒頭",
        "answer": "ぼうとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "過疎",
        "answer": "かそ"
    },
    {
        "question": "壇",
        "answer": "だん"
    },
    {
        "question": "株式",
        "answer": "かぶしき"
    },
    {
        "question": "興じる",
        "answer": "きょうじる"
    },
    {
        "question": "没落",
        "answer": "ぼつらく"
    },
    {
        "question": "結晶",
        "answer": "けっしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "滅亡",
        "answer": "めつぼう"
    },
    {
        "question": "兵士",
        "answer": "へいし"
    },
    {
        "question": "秘書",
        "answer": "ひしょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "お邪魔します",
        "answer": "おじゃまします"
    },
    {
        "question": "鉄鋼",
        "answer": "てっこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "亜科",
        "answer": "あか"
    },
    {
        "question": "救援",
        "answer": "きゅうえん"
    },
    {
        "question": "待遇",
        "answer": "たいぐう"
    },
    {
        "question": "乙",
        "answer": "おつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "精密",
        "answer": "せいみつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "尽くす",
        "answer": "つくす"
    },
    {
        "question": "独裁",
        "answer": "どくさい"
    },
    {
        "question": "交渉",
        "answer": "こうしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "爆弾",
        "answer": "ばくだん"
    },
    {
        "question": "案の定",
        "answer": "あんのじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "尚",
        "answer": "なお"
    },
    {
        "question": "元素",
        "answer": "げんそ"
    },
    {
        "question": "賄う",
        "answer": "まかなう"
    },
    {
        "question": "貨幣",
        "answer": "かへい"
    },
    {
        "question": "避難",
        "answer": "ひなん"
    },
    {
        "question": "視覚",
        "answer": "しかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "盛る",
        "answer": "さかる"
    },
    {
        "question": "代弁",
        "answer": "だいべん"
    },
    {
        "question": "志向",
        "answer": "しこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "進展",
        "answer": "しんてん"
    },
    {
        "question": "反撃",
        "answer": "はんげき"
    },
    {
        "question": "詐欺",
        "answer": "さぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "起伏",
        "answer": "きふく"
    },
    {
        "question": "反響",
        "answer": "はんきょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "廃棄",
        "answer": "はいき"
    },
    {
        "question": "推理",
        "answer": "すいり"
    },
    {
        "question": "行為",
        "answer": "こうい"
    },
    {
        "question": "慕う",
        "answer": "したう"
    },
    {
        "question": "統率",
        "answer": "とうそつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "蓮",
        "answer": "はす"
    },
    {
        "question": "弁論",
        "answer": "べんろん"
    },
    {
        "question": "運搬",
        "answer": "うんぱん"
    },
    {
        "question": "懲りる",
        "answer": "こりる"
    },
    {
        "question": "臨む",
        "answer": "のぞむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "澄ます",
        "answer": "すます"
    },
    {
        "question": "結び付く",
        "answer": "むすびつく"
    },
    {
        "question": "矢",
        "answer": "や"
    },
    {
        "question": "保護",
        "answer": "ほご"
    },
    {
        "question": "海峡",
        "answer": "かいきょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "負傷",
        "answer": "ふしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "矢っ張り",
        "answer": "やっぱり"
    },
    {
        "question": "御免なさい",
        "answer": "ごめんなさい"
    },
    {
        "question": "昆虫",
        "answer": "こんちゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "収益",
        "answer": "しゅうえき"
    },
    {
        "question": "脱する",
        "answer": "だっする"
    },
    {
        "question": "大筋",
        "answer": "おおすじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "繊維",
        "answer": "せんい"
    },
    {
        "question": "創造",
        "answer": "そうぞう"
    },
    {
        "question": "眼球",
        "answer": "がんきゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "下吏",
        "answer": "かり"
    },
    {
        "question": "折衷",
        "answer": "せっちゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "飽和",
        "answer": "ほうわ"
    },
    {
        "question": "証人",
        "answer": "しょうにん"
    },
    {
        "question": "廃止",
        "answer": "はいし"
    },
    {
        "question": "計器",
        "answer": "けいき"
    },
    {
        "question": "標語",
        "answer": "ひょうご"
    },
    {
        "question": "刑罰",
        "answer": "けいばつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "潮",
        "answer": "うしお"
    },
    {
        "question": "屎尿",
        "answer": "しにょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "掲載",
        "answer": "けいさい"
    },
    {
        "question": "緊急",
        "answer": "きんきゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "合致",
        "answer": "がっち"
    },
    {
        "question": "侮辱",
        "answer": "ぶじょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "理屈",
        "answer": "りくつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "百科辞典",
        "answer": "ひゃっかじてん"
    },
    {
        "question": "隠居",
        "answer": "いんきょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "墜落",
        "answer": "ついらく"
    },
    {
        "question": "遮る",
        "answer": "さえぎる"
    },
    {
        "question": "紛争",
        "answer": "ふんそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "真珠",
        "answer": "しんじゅ"
    },
    {
        "question": "鬱陶しい",
        "answer": "うっとうしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "褒美",
        "answer": "ほうび"
    },
    {
        "question": "於",
        "answer": "お"
    },
    {
        "question": "名簿",
        "answer": "めいぼ"
    },
    {
        "question": "同級",
        "answer": "どうきゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "監視",
        "answer": "かんし"
    },
    {
        "question": "体裁",
        "answer": "ていさい"
    },
    {
        "question": "異議",
        "answer": "いぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "凶作",
        "answer": "きょうさく"
    },
    {
        "question": "証言",
        "answer": "しょうげん"
    },
    {
        "question": "枠",
        "answer": "わく"
    },
    {
        "question": "怪獣",
        "answer": "かいじゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "激励",
        "answer": "げきれい"
    },
    {
        "question": "華美",
        "answer": "かび"
    },
    {
        "question": "滅びる",
        "answer": "ほろびる"
    },
    {
        "question": "振り",
        "answer": "ふり"
    },
    {
        "question": "その為",
        "answer": "そのため"
    },
    {
        "question": "火傷",
        "answer": "かしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "興業",
        "answer": "こうぎょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "惜しむ",
        "answer": "おしむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "模範",
        "answer": "もはん"
    },
    {
        "question": "趣",
        "answer": "おもむき"
    },
    {
        "question": "模型",
        "answer": "もけい"
    },
    {
        "question": "政策",
        "answer": "せいさく"
    },
    {
        "question": "名称",
        "answer": "めいしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "威力",
        "answer": "いりょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "拒否",
        "answer": "きょひ"
    },
    {
        "question": "幹線",
        "answer": "かんせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "特派",
        "answer": "とくは"
    },
    {
        "question": "免れる",
        "answer": "まぬかれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "製",
        "answer": "せい"
    },
    {
        "question": "据え付ける",
        "answer": "すえつける"
    },
    {
        "question": "展示",
        "answer": "てんじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "不吉",
        "answer": "ふきつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "沸騰",
        "answer": "ふっとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "事項",
        "answer": "じこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "仰っしゃる",
        "answer": "おっしゃる"
    },
    {
        "question": "潜水",
        "answer": "せんすい"
    },
    {
        "question": "添える",
        "answer": "そえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "大衆",
        "answer": "たいしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "楽譜",
        "answer": "がくふ"
    },
    {
        "question": "是非とも",
        "answer": "ぜひとも"
    },
    {
        "question": "所属",
        "answer": "しょぞく"
    },
    {
        "question": "華々しい",
        "answer": "はなばなしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "取り締まる",
        "answer": "とりしまる"
    },
    {
        "question": "緩める",
        "answer": "ゆるめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "取り扱う",
        "answer": "とりあつかう"
    },
    {
        "question": "皇居",
        "answer": "こうきょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "樹立",
        "answer": "じゅりつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "我がまま",
        "answer": "わがまま"
    },
    {
        "question": "雛",
        "answer": "ひな"
    },
    {
        "question": "孤児",
        "answer": "こじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "遣り通す",
        "answer": "やりとおす"
    },
    {
        "question": "成熟",
        "answer": "せいじゅく"
    },
    {
        "question": "浜",
        "answer": "はま"
    },
    {
        "question": "幹部",
        "answer": "かんぶ"
    },
    {
        "question": "志望",
        "answer": "しぼう"
    },
    {
        "question": "銃",
        "answer": "つつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "故人",
        "answer": "こじん"
    },
    {
        "question": "微塵",
        "answer": "みじん"
    },
    {
        "question": "倍率",
        "answer": "ばいりつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "実態",
        "answer": "じったい"
    },
    {
        "question": "奴",
        "answer": "やっこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "酸",
        "answer": "さん"
    },
    {
        "question": "粋",
        "answer": "いき"
    },
    {
        "question": "遊牧",
        "answer": "ゆうぼく"
    },
    {
        "question": "摘む",
        "answer": "つまむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "保守",
        "answer": "ほしゅ"
    },
    {
        "question": "網",
        "answer": "あみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "街",
        "answer": "がい"
    },
    {
        "question": "年鑑",
        "answer": "ねんかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "老衰",
        "answer": "ろうすい"
    },
    {
        "question": "妊娠",
        "answer": "にんしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "抗議",
        "answer": "こうぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "奨励",
        "answer": "しょうれい"
    },
    {
        "question": "象徴",
        "answer": "しょうちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "故",
        "answer": "こ"
    },
    {
        "question": "連邦",
        "answer": "れんぽう"
    },
    {
        "question": "密か",
        "answer": "ひそか"
    },
    {
        "question": "企画",
        "answer": "きかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "短縮",
        "answer": "たんしゅく"
    },
    {
        "question": "刑",
        "answer": "けい"
    },
    {
        "question": "葬る",
        "answer": "ほうむる"
    },
    {
        "question": "共稼ぎ",
        "answer": "ともかせぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "賠償",
        "answer": "ばいしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "獣",
        "answer": "けだもの"
    },
    {
        "question": "偏見",
        "answer": "へんけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "装飾",
        "answer": "そうしょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "盲点",
        "answer": "もうてん"
    },
    {
        "question": "陶器",
        "answer": "とうき"
    },
    {
        "question": "間柄",
        "answer": "あいだがら"
    },
    {
        "question": "近視",
        "answer": "きんし"
    },
    {
        "question": "藍褸",
        "answer": "ぼろ"
    },
    {
        "question": "やり遂げる",
        "answer": "やりとげる"
    },
    {
        "question": "麻痺",
        "answer": "まひ"
    },
    {
        "question": "同士",
        "answer": "どうし"
    },
    {
        "question": "利潤",
        "answer": "りじゅん"
    },
    {
        "question": "拝啓",
        "answer": "はいけい"
    },
    {
        "question": "養う",
        "answer": "やしなう"
    },
    {
        "question": "慎む",
        "answer": "つつしむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "訴訟",
        "answer": "そしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "核",
        "answer": "かく"
    },
    {
        "question": "励ます",
        "answer": "はげます"
    },
    {
        "question": "鞠",
        "answer": "まり"
    },
    {
        "question": "小柄",
        "answer": "こがら"
    },
    {
        "question": "峰",
        "answer": "みね"
    },
    {
        "question": "蓄積",
        "answer": "ちくせき"
    },
    {
        "question": "征服",
        "answer": "せいふく"
    },
    {
        "question": "観衆",
        "answer": "かんしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "差異",
        "answer": "さい"
    },
    {
        "question": "氾濫",
        "answer": "はんらん"
    },
    {
        "question": "素材",
        "answer": "そざい"
    },
    {
        "question": "詳細",
        "answer": "しょうさい"
    },
    {
        "question": "胴",
        "answer": "どう"
    },
    {
        "question": "改訂",
        "answer": "かいてい"
    },
    {
        "question": "露",
        "answer": "つゆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "振動",
        "answer": "しんどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "停滞",
        "answer": "ていたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "破棄",
        "answer": "はき"
    },
    {
        "question": "裁く",
        "answer": "さばく"
    },
    {
        "question": "排除",
        "answer": "はいじょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "統制",
        "answer": "とうせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "享受",
        "answer": "きょうじゅ"
    },
    {
        "question": "訂正",
        "answer": "ていせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "対応",
        "answer": "たいおう"
    },
    {
        "question": "目盛",
        "answer": "めもり"
    },
    {
        "question": "色彩",
        "answer": "しきさい"
    },
    {
        "question": "適宜",
        "answer": "てきぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "乃至",
        "answer": "ないし"
    },
    {
        "question": "幹",
        "answer": "かん"
    },
    {
        "question": "書評",
        "answer": "しょひょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "漏らす",
        "answer": "もらす"
    },
    {
        "question": "是正",
        "answer": "ぜせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "上司",
        "answer": "じょうし"
    },
    {
        "question": "呉れ呉れも",
        "answer": "くれぐれも"
    },
    {
        "question": "誤魔化す",
        "answer": "ごまかす"
    },
    {
        "question": "屋敷",
        "answer": "やしき"
    },
    {
        "question": "大柄",
        "answer": "おおがら"
    },
    {
        "question": "修学",
        "answer": "しゅうがく"
    },
    {
        "question": "紡績",
        "answer": "ぼうせき"
    },
    {
        "question": "愚か",
        "answer": "おろか"
    },
    {
        "question": "漏る",
        "answer": "もる"
    },
    {
        "question": "衆議院",
        "answer": "しゅうぎいん"
    },
    {
        "question": "指摘",
        "answer": "してき"
    },
    {
        "question": "自己",
        "answer": "じこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "死刑",
        "answer": "しけい"
    },
    {
        "question": "地獄",
        "answer": "じごく"
    },
    {
        "question": "提供",
        "answer": "ていきょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "惨め",
        "answer": "みじめ"
    },
    {
        "question": "同盟",
        "answer": "どうめい"
    },
    {
        "question": "厳か",
        "answer": "おごそか"
    },
    {
        "question": "茎",
        "answer": "くき"
    },
    {
        "question": "獲得",
        "answer": "かくとく"
    },
    {
        "question": "粘る",
        "answer": "ねばる"
    },
    {
        "question": "器官",
        "answer": "きかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "陰気",
        "answer": "いんき"
    },
    {
        "question": "促す",
        "answer": "うながす"
    },
    {
        "question": "継ぎ目",
        "answer": "つぎめ"
    },
    {
        "question": "貫禄",
        "answer": "かんろく"
    },
    {
        "question": "膨脹",
        "answer": "ぼうちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "揺さぶる",
        "answer": "ゆさぶる"
    },
    {
        "question": "略奪",
        "answer": "りゃくだつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "丁目",
        "answer": "ちょうめ"
    },
    {
        "question": "一概に",
        "answer": "いちがいに"
    },
    {
        "question": "脚本",
        "answer": "きゃくほん"
    },
    {
        "question": "緩む",
        "answer": "ゆるむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "弁解",
        "answer": "べんかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "憧れ",
        "answer": "あこがれ"
    },
    {
        "question": "霞む",
        "answer": "かすむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "酷い",
        "answer": "ひどい"
    },
    {
        "question": "驚き",
        "answer": "おどろき"
    },
    {
        "question": "焦げ茶",
        "answer": "こげちゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "沿う",
        "answer": "そう"
    },
    {
        "question": "風俗",
        "answer": "ふうぞく"
    },
    {
        "question": "誇る",
        "answer": "ほこる"
    },
    {
        "question": "貴い",
        "answer": "たっとい"
    },
    {
        "question": "繁殖",
        "answer": "はんしょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "製鉄",
        "answer": "せいてつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "守衛",
        "answer": "しゅえい"
    },
    {
        "question": "鍛える",
        "answer": "きたえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "弁護",
        "answer": "べんご"
    },
    {
        "question": "譲歩",
        "answer": "じょうほ"
    },
    {
        "question": "勇敢",
        "answer": "ゆうかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "態と",
        "answer": "わざと"
    },
    {
        "question": "錯覚",
        "answer": "さっかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "謙る",
        "answer": "へりくだる"
    },
    {
        "question": "冴える",
        "answer": "さえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "懐く",
        "answer": "なつく"
    },
    {
        "question": "滞る",
        "answer": "とどこおる"
    },
    {
        "question": "至って",
        "answer": "いたって"
    },
    {
        "question": "遂げる",
        "answer": "とげる"
    },
    {
        "question": "長閑",
        "answer": "のどか"
    },
    {
        "question": "獲物",
        "answer": "えもの"
    },
    {
        "question": "規模",
        "answer": "きぼ"
    },
    {
        "question": "明瞭",
        "answer": "めいりょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "遣い",
        "answer": "つかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "異論",
        "answer": "いろん"
    },
    {
        "question": "控除",
        "answer": "こうじょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "挑戦",
        "answer": "ちょうせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "箇条書き",
        "answer": "かじょうがき"
    },
    {
        "question": "充実",
        "answer": "じゅうじつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "肺",
        "answer": "はい"
    },
    {
        "question": "納まる",
        "answer": "おさまる"
    },
    {
        "question": "警戒",
        "answer": "けいかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "防衛",
        "answer": "ぼうえい"
    },
    {
        "question": "舗装",
        "answer": "ほそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "月謝",
        "answer": "げっしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "驚異",
        "answer": "きょうい"
    },
    {
        "question": "発芽",
        "answer": "はつが"
    },
    {
        "question": "恵み",
        "answer": "めぐみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "徐行",
        "answer": "じょこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "規範",
        "answer": "きはん"
    },
    {
        "question": "眉",
        "answer": "まゆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "尉",
        "answer": "じょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "処罰",
        "answer": "しょばつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "誠",
        "answer": "まこと"
    },
    {
        "question": "歓声",
        "answer": "かんせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "幽霊",
        "answer": "ゆうれい"
    },
    {
        "question": "比率",
        "answer": "ひりつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "修行",
        "answer": "しゅうぎょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "励む",
        "answer": "はげむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "冷酷",
        "answer": "れいこく"
    },
    {
        "question": "強請る",
        "answer": "ねだる"
    },
    {
        "question": "志",
        "answer": "こころざし"
    },
    {
        "question": "肥料",
        "answer": "ひりょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "馬鹿馬鹿しい",
        "answer": "ばかばかしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "境遇",
        "answer": "きょうぐう"
    },
    {
        "question": "刃",
        "answer": "は"
    },
    {
        "question": "結び",
        "answer": "むすび"
    },
    {
        "question": "着飾る",
        "answer": "きかざる"
    },
    {
        "question": "憂鬱",
        "answer": "ゆううつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "描写",
        "answer": "びょうしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "傑",
        "answer": "けつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "視察",
        "answer": "しさつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "戯曲",
        "answer": "ぎきょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "契る",
        "answer": "ちぎる"
    },
    {
        "question": "鮮やか",
        "answer": "あざやか"
    },
    {
        "question": "冷淡",
        "answer": "れいたん"
    },
    {
        "question": "遭難",
        "answer": "そうなん"
    },
    {
        "question": "誠実",
        "answer": "せいじつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "中継",
        "answer": "ちゅうけい"
    },
    {
        "question": "拘束",
        "answer": "こうそく"
    },
    {
        "question": "団結",
        "answer": "だんけつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "権威",
        "answer": "けんい"
    },
    {
        "question": "購買",
        "answer": "こうばい"
    },
    {
        "question": "概説",
        "answer": "がいせつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "報酬",
        "answer": "ほうしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "噴出",
        "answer": "ふんしゅつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "窒息",
        "answer": "ちっそく"
    },
    {
        "question": "衛生",
        "answer": "えいせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "暴露",
        "answer": "ばくろ"
    },
    {
        "question": "頻繁",
        "answer": "ひんぱん"
    },
    {
        "question": "必修",
        "answer": "ひっしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "神秘",
        "answer": "しんぴ"
    },
    {
        "question": "耐える",
        "answer": "たえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "丁々",
        "answer": "とうとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "御免ください",
        "answer": "ごめんください"
    },
    {
        "question": "志す",
        "answer": "こころざす"
    },
    {
        "question": "倹約",
        "answer": "けんやく"
    },
    {
        "question": "軌道",
        "answer": "きどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "愚痴",
        "answer": "ぐち"
    },
    {
        "question": "如何にも",
        "answer": "いかにも"
    },
    {
        "question": "団扇",
        "answer": "うちわ"
    },
    {
        "question": "結び付き",
        "answer": "むすびつき"
    },
    {
        "question": "応募",
        "answer": "おうぼ"
    },
    {
        "question": "久し振り",
        "answer": "ひさしぶり"
    },
    {
        "question": "誘導",
        "answer": "ゆうどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "駆ける",
        "answer": "かける"
    },
    {
        "question": "津波",
        "answer": "つなみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "統治",
        "answer": "とうじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "概念",
        "answer": "がいねん"
    },
    {
        "question": "不振",
        "answer": "ふしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "迫害",
        "answer": "はくがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "粘り",
        "answer": "ねばり"
    },
    {
        "question": "碁盤",
        "answer": "ごばん"
    },
    {
        "question": "微笑",
        "answer": "びしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "相応しい",
        "answer": "ふさわしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "恵む",
        "answer": "めぐむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "票",
        "answer": "ひょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "丘陵",
        "answer": "きゅうりょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "改修",
        "answer": "かいしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "証拠",
        "answer": "しょうこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "密度",
        "answer": "みつど"
    },
    {
        "question": "財源",
        "answer": "ざいげん"
    },
    {
        "question": "幕",
        "answer": "とばり"
    },
    {
        "question": "張り紙",
        "answer": "はりがみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "迅速",
        "answer": "じんそく"
    },
    {
        "question": "細胞",
        "answer": "さいぼう"
    },
    {
        "question": "事柄",
        "answer": "ことがら"
    },
    {
        "question": "宣教",
        "answer": "せんきょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "一寸",
        "answer": "ちょっと"
    },
    {
        "question": "無邪気",
        "answer": "むじゃき"
    },
    {
        "question": "庶民",
        "answer": "しょみん"
    },
    {
        "question": "蝶",
        "answer": "ちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "健やか",
        "answer": "すこやか"
    },
    {
        "question": "尾",
        "answer": "お"
    },
    {
        "question": "御覧なさい",
        "answer": "ごらんなさい"
    },
    {
        "question": "即ち",
        "answer": "すなわち"
    },
    {
        "question": "還暦",
        "answer": "かんれき"
    },
    {
        "question": "紛れる",
        "answer": "まぎれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "炭素",
        "answer": "たんそ"
    },
    {
        "question": "阻止",
        "answer": "そし"
    },
    {
        "question": "矢鱈に",
        "answer": "やたらに"
    },
    {
        "question": "捕吏",
        "answer": "ほり"
    },
    {
        "question": "派遣",
        "answer": "はけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "庶務",
        "answer": "しょむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "窮屈",
        "answer": "きゅうくつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "極端",
        "answer": "きょくたん"
    },
    {
        "question": "貯蓄",
        "answer": "ちょちく"
    },
    {
        "question": "奇数",
        "answer": "きすう"
    },
    {
        "question": "不評",
        "answer": "ふひょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "還元",
        "answer": "かんげん"
    },
    {
        "question": "授ける",
        "answer": "さずける"
    },
    {
        "question": "提示",
        "answer": "ていじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "審判",
        "answer": "しんばん"
    },
    {
        "question": "指揮",
        "answer": "しき"
    },
    {
        "question": "結成",
        "answer": "けっせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "模倣",
        "answer": "もほう"
    },
    {
        "question": "証",
        "answer": "あかし"
    },
    {
        "question": "じゃん拳",
        "answer": "じゃんけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "疾っくに",
        "answer": "とっくに"
    },
    {
        "question": "渦",
        "answer": "うず"
    },
    {
        "question": "如何して",
        "answer": "どうして"
    },
    {
        "question": "微量",
        "answer": "びりょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "如何に",
        "answer": "いかに"
    },
    {
        "question": "整列",
        "answer": "せいれつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "悲惨",
        "answer": "ひさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "円滑",
        "answer": "えんかつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "座標",
        "answer": "ざひょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "保障",
        "answer": "ほしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "跡継ぎ",
        "answer": "あとつぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "班",
        "answer": "はん"
    },
    {
        "question": "祝賀",
        "answer": "しゅくが"
    },
    {
        "question": "主催",
        "answer": "しゅさい"
    },
    {
        "question": "漏れる",
        "answer": "もれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "脅す",
        "answer": "おどす"
    },
    {
        "question": "携わる",
        "answer": "たずさわる"
    },
    {
        "question": "善良",
        "answer": "ぜんりょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "結び付ける",
        "answer": "むすびつける"
    },
    {
        "question": "密接",
        "answer": "みっせつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "侵す",
        "answer": "おかす"
    },
    {
        "question": "近眼",
        "answer": "きんがん"
    },
    {
        "question": "障る",
        "answer": "さわる"
    },
    {
        "question": "素敵",
        "answer": "すてき"
    },
    {
        "question": "荒廃",
        "answer": "こうはい"
    },
    {
        "question": "整える",
        "answer": "ととのえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "称する",
        "answer": "しょうする"
    },
    {
        "question": "措置",
        "answer": "そち"
    },
    {
        "question": "卑しい",
        "answer": "いやしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "拐う",
        "answer": "さらう"
    },
    {
        "question": "根拠",
        "answer": "こんきょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "貝殻",
        "answer": "かいがら"
    },
    {
        "question": "駄作",
        "answer": "ださく"
    },
    {
        "question": "仰ぐ",
        "answer": "あおぐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "福祉",
        "answer": "ふくし"
    },
    {
        "question": "振り出し",
        "answer": "ふりだし"
    },
    {
        "question": "疎か",
        "answer": "おろそか"
    },
    {
        "question": "磁器",
        "answer": "じき"
    },
    {
        "question": "藻掻く",
        "answer": "もがく"
    },
    {
        "question": "聴講",
        "answer": "ちょうこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "街道",
        "answer": "かいどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "好評",
        "answer": "こうひょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "お巡りさん",
        "answer": "おまわりさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "展望",
        "answer": "てんぼう"
    },
    {
        "question": "英雄",
        "answer": "えいゆう"
    },
    {
        "question": "脈",
        "answer": "みゃく"
    },
    {
        "question": "暇",
        "answer": "いとま"
    },
    {
        "question": "連盟",
        "answer": "れんめい"
    },
    {
        "question": "妥協",
        "answer": "だきょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "朗読",
        "answer": "ろうどく"
    },
    {
        "question": "器",
        "answer": "うつわ"
    },
    {
        "question": "修飾",
        "answer": "しゅうしょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "花壇",
        "answer": "かだん"
    },
    {
        "question": "既婚",
        "answer": "きこん"
    },
    {
        "question": "偏",
        "answer": "へん"
    },
    {
        "question": "緩やか",
        "answer": "ゆるやか"
    },
    {
        "question": "漂う",
        "answer": "ただよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "掌",
        "answer": "たなごころ"
    },
    {
        "question": "保つ",
        "answer": "たもつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "感染",
        "answer": "かんせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "勧め",
        "answer": "すすめ"
    },
    {
        "question": "腐敗",
        "answer": "ふはい"
    },
    {
        "question": "微か",
        "answer": "かすか"
    },
    {
        "question": "玄人",
        "answer": "くろうと"
    },
    {
        "question": "小銭",
        "answer": "こぜに"
    },
    {
        "question": "市街",
        "answer": "しがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "取り扱い",
        "answer": "とりあつかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "宣言",
        "answer": "せんげん"
    },
    {
        "question": "妨害",
        "answer": "ぼうがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "及ぶ",
        "answer": "およぶ"
    },
    {
        "question": "節",
        "answer": "せつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "諮る",
        "answer": "はかる"
    },
    {
        "question": "該当",
        "answer": "がいとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "結合",
        "answer": "けつごう"
    },
    {
        "question": "余興",
        "answer": "よきょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "異動",
        "answer": "いどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "妥結",
        "answer": "だけつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "縁",
        "answer": "えん"
    },
    {
        "question": "言い訳",
        "answer": "いいわけ"
    },
    {
        "question": "圧迫",
        "answer": "あっぱく"
    },
    {
        "question": "富豪",
        "answer": "ふごう"
    },
    {
        "question": "語源",
        "answer": "ごげん"
    },
    {
        "question": "勘弁",
        "answer": "かんべん"
    },
    {
        "question": "統合",
        "answer": "とうごう"
    },
    {
        "question": "華奢",
        "answer": "かしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "第一",
        "answer": "だいいち"
    },
    {
        "question": "第",
        "answer": "だい"
    },
    {
        "question": "駆け足",
        "answer": "かけあし"
    },
    {
        "question": "担架",
        "answer": "たんか"
    },
    {
        "question": "確保",
        "answer": "かくほ"
    },
    {
        "question": "原典",
        "answer": "げんてん"
    },
    {
        "question": "変遷",
        "answer": "へんせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "何故なら",
        "answer": "なぜなら"
    },
    {
        "question": "全盛",
        "answer": "ぜんせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "独自",
        "answer": "どくじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "内訳",
        "answer": "うちわけ"
    },
    {
        "question": "相応",
        "answer": "そうおう"
    },
    {
        "question": "頑丈",
        "answer": "がんじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "徹する",
        "answer": "てっする"
    },
    {
        "question": "敢えて",
        "answer": "あえて"
    },
    {
        "question": "締め切り",
        "answer": "しめきり"
    },
    {
        "question": "頑固",
        "answer": "がんこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "阻む",
        "answer": "はばむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "前提",
        "answer": "ぜんてい"
    },
    {
        "question": "駆けっこ",
        "answer": "かけっこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "馬鹿らしい",
        "answer": "ばからしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "赴く",
        "answer": "おもむく"
    },
    {
        "question": "酸っぱい",
        "answer": "すっぱい"
    },
    {
        "question": "汽船",
        "answer": "きせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "選挙",
        "answer": "せんきょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "率いる",
        "answer": "ひきいる"
    },
    {
        "question": "可哀想",
        "answer": "かわいそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "気兼ね",
        "answer": "きがね"
    },
    {
        "question": "添う",
        "answer": "そう"
    },
    {
        "question": "簡潔",
        "answer": "かんけつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "繁栄",
        "answer": "はんえい"
    },
    {
        "question": "気障",
        "answer": "きざ"
    },
    {
        "question": "健全",
        "answer": "けんぜん"
    },
    {
        "question": "肝心",
        "answer": "かんじん"
    },
    {
        "question": "眼鏡",
        "answer": "がんきょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "首飾り",
        "answer": "くびかざり"
    },
    {
        "question": "定義",
        "answer": "ていぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "手錠",
        "answer": "てじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "悪戯",
        "answer": "いたずら"
    },
    {
        "question": "婿",
        "answer": "むこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "凡ゆる",
        "answer": "あらゆる"
    },
    {
        "question": "打撃",
        "answer": "だげき"
    },
    {
        "question": "救済",
        "answer": "きゅうさい"
    },
    {
        "question": "弾む",
        "answer": "はずむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "泌み泌み",
        "answer": "しみじみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "佐",
        "answer": "さ"
    },
    {
        "question": "契機",
        "answer": "けいき"
    },
    {
        "question": "桟橋",
        "answer": "さんきょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "進呈",
        "answer": "しんてい"
    },
    {
        "question": "僧",
        "answer": "そう"
    },
    {
        "question": "質素",
        "answer": "しっそ"
    },
    {
        "question": "新興",
        "answer": "しんこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "不山戯る",
        "answer": "ふざける"
    },
    {
        "question": "戦災",
        "answer": "せんさい"
    },
    {
        "question": "負債",
        "answer": "ふさい"
    },
    {
        "question": "膜",
        "answer": "まく"
    },
    {
        "question": "甲",
        "answer": "きのえ"
    },
    {
        "question": "扶養",
        "answer": "ふよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "弁償",
        "answer": "べんしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "山岳",
        "answer": "さんがく"
    },
    {
        "question": "清濁",
        "answer": "せいだく"
    },
    {
        "question": "崇拝",
        "answer": "すうはい"
    },
    {
        "question": "膨れる",
        "answer": "ふくれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "沈没",
        "answer": "ちんぼつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "攻め",
        "answer": "せめ"
    },
    {
        "question": "奉仕",
        "answer": "ほうし"
    },
    {
        "question": "光沢",
        "answer": "こうたく"
    },
    {
        "question": "徐々",
        "answer": "そろそろ"
    },
    {
        "question": "芝",
        "answer": "しば"
    },
    {
        "question": "脅かす",
        "answer": "おどかす"
    },
    {
        "question": "生臭い",
        "answer": "なまぐさい"
    },
    {
        "question": "興奮",
        "answer": "こうふん"
    },
    {
        "question": "雌",
        "answer": "めす"
    },
    {
        "question": "神聖",
        "answer": "しんせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "仮令",
        "answer": "たとえ"
    },
    {
        "question": "法廷",
        "answer": "ほうてい"
    },
    {
        "question": "探検",
        "answer": "たんけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "弾く",
        "answer": "はじく"
    },
    {
        "question": "明朗",
        "answer": "めいろう"
    },
    {
        "question": "襟",
        "answer": "えり"
    },
    {
        "question": "脅迫",
        "answer": "きょうはく"
    },
    {
        "question": "結核",
        "answer": "けっかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "聴覚",
        "answer": "ちょうかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "盛装",
        "answer": "せいそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "覆す",
        "answer": "くつがえす"
    },
    {
        "question": "聖書",
        "answer": "せいしょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "懸賞",
        "answer": "けんしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "回覧",
        "answer": "かいらん"
    },
    {
        "question": "視点",
        "answer": "してん"
    },
    {
        "question": "脱出",
        "answer": "だっしゅつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "普遍",
        "answer": "ふへん"
    },
    {
        "question": "従来",
        "answer": "じゅうらい"
    },
    {
        "question": "兼業",
        "answer": "けんぎょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "天井",
        "answer": "てんじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "方策",
        "answer": "ほうさく"
    },
    {
        "question": "街頭",
        "answer": "がいとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "滅ぼす",
        "answer": "ほろぼす"
    },
    {
        "question": "潤う",
        "answer": "うるおう"
    },
    {
        "question": "合併",
        "answer": "がっぺい"
    },
    {
        "question": "不審",
        "answer": "ふしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "看護",
        "answer": "かんご"
    },
    {
        "question": "凌ぐ",
        "answer": "しのぐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "対抗",
        "answer": "たいこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "破壊",
        "answer": "はかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "縁側",
        "answer": "えんがわ"
    },
    {
        "question": "観覧",
        "answer": "かんらん"
    },
    {
        "question": "護衛",
        "answer": "ごえい"
    },
    {
        "question": "凝らす",
        "answer": "こごらす"
    },
    {
        "question": "悟る",
        "answer": "さとる"
    },
    {
        "question": "傷付く",
        "answer": "きずつく"
    },
    {
        "question": "紳士",
        "answer": "しんし"
    },
    {
        "question": "余暇",
        "answer": "よか"
    },
    {
        "question": "軽率",
        "answer": "けいそつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "条約",
        "answer": "じょうやく"
    },
    {
        "question": "提携",
        "answer": "ていけい"
    },
    {
        "question": "にも拘らず",
        "answer": "にもかかわらず"
    },
    {
        "question": "滑らか",
        "answer": "なめらか"
    },
    {
        "question": "憤慨",
        "answer": "ふんがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "屈折",
        "answer": "くっせつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "梅干",
        "answer": "うめぼし"
    },
    {
        "question": "徴収",
        "answer": "ちょうしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "義理",
        "answer": "ぎり"
    },
    {
        "question": "操る",
        "answer": "あやつる"
    },
    {
        "question": "検事",
        "answer": "けんじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "捕獲",
        "answer": "ほかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "納入",
        "answer": "のうにゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "土俵",
        "answer": "どひょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "惑星",
        "answer": "わくせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "法案",
        "answer": "ほうあん"
    },
    {
        "question": "襲撃",
        "answer": "しゅうげき"
    },
    {
        "question": "推測",
        "answer": "すいそく"
    },
    {
        "question": "飼育",
        "answer": "しいく"
    },
    {
        "question": "窮乏",
        "answer": "きゅうぼう"
    },
    {
        "question": "語句",
        "answer": "ごく"
    },
    {
        "question": "専修",
        "answer": "せんしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "審査",
        "answer": "しんさ"
    },
    {
        "question": "聴診器",
        "answer": "ちょうしんき"
    },
    {
        "question": "購読",
        "answer": "こうどく"
    },
    {
        "question": "栽培",
        "answer": "さいばい"
    },
    {
        "question": "要請",
        "answer": "ようせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "保養",
        "answer": "ほよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "敏感",
        "answer": "びんかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "腸",
        "answer": "ちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "勧告",
        "answer": "かんこく"
    },
    {
        "question": "襲う",
        "answer": "おそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "内閣",
        "answer": "ないかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "巧妙",
        "answer": "こうみょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "濫用",
        "answer": "らんよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "兼ねて",
        "answer": "かねて"
    },
    {
        "question": "発条",
        "answer": "ばね"
    },
    {
        "question": "保母",
        "answer": "ほぼ"
    },
    {
        "question": "携帯",
        "answer": "けいたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "消耗",
        "answer": "しょうこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "廃れる",
        "answer": "すたれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "追及",
        "answer": "ついきゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "即座に",
        "answer": "そくざに"
    },
    {
        "question": "抑圧",
        "answer": "よくあつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "融資",
        "answer": "ゆうし"
    },
    {
        "question": "結束",
        "answer": "けっそく"
    },
    {
        "question": "創立",
        "answer": "そうりつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "伊井",
        "answer": "いい"
    },
    {
        "question": "視野",
        "answer": "しや"
    },
    {
        "question": "崩壊",
        "answer": "ほうかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "壮大",
        "answer": "そうだい"
    },
    {
        "question": "履歴",
        "answer": "りれき"
    },
    {
        "question": "捕鯨",
        "answer": "ほげい"
    },
    {
        "question": "郷里",
        "answer": "きょうり"
    },
    {
        "question": "司法",
        "answer": "しほう"
    },
    {
        "question": "雷",
        "answer": "いかずち"
    },
    {
        "question": "匹敵",
        "answer": "ひってき"
    },
    {
        "question": "保管",
        "answer": "ほかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "嘆く",
        "answer": "なげく"
    },
    {
        "question": "秩序",
        "answer": "ちつじょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "梢",
        "answer": "こずえ"
    },
    {
        "question": "煩わしい",
        "answer": "わずらわしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "残酷",
        "answer": "ざんこく"
    },
    {
        "question": "解剖",
        "answer": "かいぼう"
    },
    {
        "question": "唱える",
        "answer": "となえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "且つ",
        "answer": "かつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "帳",
        "answer": "とばり"
    },
    {
        "question": "天災",
        "answer": "てんさい"
    },
    {
        "question": "どうぞ宜しく",
        "answer": "どうぞよろしく"
    },
    {
        "question": "沈黙",
        "answer": "ちんもく"
    },
    {
        "question": "漠然",
        "answer": "ばくぜん"
    },
    {
        "question": "就業",
        "answer": "しゅうぎょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "制裁",
        "answer": "せいさい"
    },
    {
        "question": "救い",
        "answer": "すくい"
    },
    {
        "question": "善し悪し",
        "answer": "よしあし"
    },
    {
        "question": "放射",
        "answer": "ほうしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "衰える",
        "answer": "おとろえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "偽造",
        "answer": "ぎぞう"
    },
    {
        "question": "暦",
        "answer": "こよみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "司る",
        "answer": "つかさどる"
    },
    {
        "question": "欺く",
        "answer": "あざむく"
    },
    {
        "question": "修士",
        "answer": "しゅうし"
    },
    {
        "question": "紛失",
        "answer": "ふんしつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "議案",
        "answer": "ぎあん"
    },
    {
        "question": "開拓",
        "answer": "かいたく"
    },
    {
        "question": "健在",
        "answer": "けんざい"
    },
    {
        "question": "捕虜",
        "answer": "ほりょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "逸らす",
        "answer": "そらす"
    },
    {
        "question": "棄権",
        "answer": "きけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "感慨",
        "answer": "かんがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "源",
        "answer": "みなもと"
    },
    {
        "question": "運賃",
        "answer": "うんちん"
    },
    {
        "question": "系",
        "answer": "けい"
    },
    {
        "question": "突っ張る",
        "answer": "つっぱる"
    },
    {
        "question": "黴菌",
        "answer": "ばいきん"
    },
    {
        "question": "控える",
        "answer": "ひかえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "於いて",
        "answer": "おいて"
    },
    {
        "question": "僕",
        "answer": "しもべ"
    },
    {
        "question": "隔週",
        "answer": "かくしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "異見",
        "answer": "いけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "簡素",
        "answer": "かんそ"
    },
    {
        "question": "据える",
        "answer": "すえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "眼科",
        "answer": "がんか"
    },
    {
        "question": "染まる",
        "answer": "そまる"
    },
    {
        "question": "扱い",
        "answer": "あつかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "苗",
        "answer": "なえ"
    },
    {
        "question": "鉛",
        "answer": "なまり"
    },
    {
        "question": "合唱",
        "answer": "がっしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "拒絶",
        "answer": "きょぜつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "後悔",
        "answer": "こうかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "麻",
        "answer": "あさ"
    },
    {
        "question": "名誉",
        "answer": "めいよ"
    },
    {
        "question": "傷",
        "answer": "しょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "酪農",
        "answer": "らくのう"
    },
    {
        "question": "拡散",
        "answer": "かくさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "嬢",
        "answer": "じょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "露骨",
        "answer": "ろこつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "滞納",
        "answer": "たいのう"
    },
    {
        "question": "抗争",
        "answer": "こうそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "及び",
        "answer": "および"
    },
    {
        "question": "尿",
        "answer": "にょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "操縦",
        "answer": "そうじゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "最善",
        "answer": "さいぜん"
    },
    {
        "question": "訴え",
        "answer": "うったえ"
    },
    {
        "question": "邸宅",
        "answer": "ていたく"
    },
    {
        "question": "散蒔く",
        "answer": "ばらまく"
    },
    {
        "question": "朽ちる",
        "answer": "くちる"
    },
    {
        "question": "尚更",
        "answer": "なおさら"
    },
    {
        "question": "養成",
        "answer": "ようせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "墓地",
        "answer": "はかち"
    },
    {
        "question": "症",
        "answer": "しょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "騒動",
        "answer": "そうどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "赴任",
        "answer": "ふにん"
    },
    {
        "question": "推進",
        "answer": "すいしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "氏",
        "answer": "うじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "欠乏",
        "answer": "けつぼう"
    },
    {
        "question": "猛烈",
        "answer": "もうれつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "為さる",
        "answer": "なさる"
    },
    {
        "question": "創刊",
        "answer": "そうかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "免除",
        "answer": "めんじょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "従事",
        "answer": "じゅうじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "麻酔",
        "answer": "ますい"
    },
    {
        "question": "宮殿",
        "answer": "きゅうでん"
    },
    {
        "question": "几帳面",
        "answer": "きちょうめん"
    },
    {
        "question": "返還",
        "answer": "へんかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "遣る",
        "answer": "やる"
    },
    {
        "question": "化繊",
        "answer": "かせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "均衡",
        "answer": "きんこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "擦る",
        "answer": "かする"
    },
    {
        "question": "破裂",
        "answer": "はれつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "犠牲",
        "answer": "ぎせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "寛容",
        "answer": "かんよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "大概",
        "answer": "たいがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "誇張",
        "answer": "こちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "身振り",
        "answer": "みぶり"
    },
    {
        "question": "封鎖",
        "answer": "ふうさ"
    },
    {
        "question": "審議",
        "answer": "しんぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "捜索",
        "answer": "そうさく"
    },
    {
        "question": "率直",
        "answer": "そっちょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "討論",
        "answer": "とうろん"
    },
    {
        "question": "全滅",
        "answer": "ぜんめつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "民俗",
        "answer": "みんぞく"
    },
    {
        "question": "大胆",
        "answer": "だいたん"
    },
    {
        "question": "箇箇",
        "answer": "ここ"
    },
    {
        "question": "承諾",
        "answer": "しょうだく"
    },
    {
        "question": "保険",
        "answer": "ほけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "一括",
        "answer": "いっかつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "分離",
        "answer": "ぶんり"
    },
    {
        "question": "牧師",
        "answer": "ぼくし"
    },
    {
        "question": "記載",
        "answer": "きさい"
    },
    {
        "question": "等級",
        "answer": "とうきゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "奮闘",
        "answer": "ふんとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "採択",
        "answer": "さいたく"
    },
    {
        "question": "華やか",
        "answer": "はなやか"
    },
    {
        "question": "戦闘",
        "answer": "せんとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "奇麗",
        "answer": "きれい"
    },
    {
        "question": "仮",
        "answer": "か"
    },
    {
        "question": "受け継ぐ",
        "answer": "うけつぐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "疑惑",
        "answer": "ぎわく"
    },
    {
        "question": "呉れる",
        "answer": "くれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "中傷",
        "answer": "ちゅうしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "裂ける",
        "answer": "さける"
    },
    {
        "question": "学士",
        "answer": "がくし"
    },
    {
        "question": "未熟",
        "answer": "みじゅく"
    },
    {
        "question": "堤防",
        "answer": "ていぼう"
    },
    {
        "question": "何故",
        "answer": "なぜ"
    },
    {
        "question": "忠告",
        "answer": "ちゅうこく"
    },
    {
        "question": "怠い",
        "answer": "だるい"
    },
    {
        "question": "染める",
        "answer": "そめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "釣り",
        "answer": "つり"
    },
    {
        "question": "分裂",
        "answer": "ぶんれつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "衆",
        "answer": "しゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "独創",
        "answer": "どくそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "動揺",
        "answer": "どうよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "経緯",
        "answer": "いきさつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "案じる",
        "answer": "あんじる"
    },
    {
        "question": "罰",
        "answer": "ばち"
    },
    {
        "question": "諄い",
        "answer": "くどい"
    },
    {
        "question": "閉鎖",
        "answer": "へいさ"
    },
    {
        "question": "百科事典",
        "answer": "ひゃっかじてん"
    },
    {
        "question": "繁盛",
        "answer": "はんじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "山脈",
        "answer": "さんみゃく"
    },
    {
        "question": "覆面",
        "answer": "ふくめん"
    },
    {
        "question": "吟味",
        "answer": "ぎんみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "船舶",
        "answer": "せんぱく"
    },
    {
        "question": "独占",
        "answer": "どくせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "開催",
        "answer": "かいさい"
    },
    {
        "question": "盛り上がる",
        "answer": "もりあがる"
    },
    {
        "question": "陳列",
        "answer": "ちんれつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "没収",
        "answer": "ぼっしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "織物",
        "answer": "おりもの"
    },
    {
        "question": "踏まえる",
        "answer": "ふまえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "益々",
        "answer": "ますます"
    },
    {
        "question": "施設",
        "answer": "しせつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "放棄",
        "answer": "ほうき"
    },
    {
        "question": "塾",
        "answer": "じゅく"
    },
    {
        "question": "賃金",
        "answer": "ちんぎん"
    },
    {
        "question": "錯誤",
        "answer": "さくご"
    },
    {
        "question": "垂れる",
        "answer": "たれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "哉",
        "answer": "や"
    },
    {
        "question": "浸す",
        "answer": "ひたす"
    },
    {
        "question": "暫く",
        "answer": "しばらく"
    },
    {
        "question": "孤独",
        "answer": "こどく"
    },
    {
        "question": "為来り",
        "answer": "しきたり"
    },
    {
        "question": "親善",
        "answer": "しんぜん"
    },
    {
        "question": "扉",
        "answer": "とびら"
    },
    {
        "question": "潜る",
        "answer": "くぐる"
    },
    {
        "question": "繕う",
        "answer": "つくろう"
    },
    {
        "question": "仙",
        "answer": "せん"
    },
    {
        "question": "爽やか",
        "answer": "さわやか"
    },
    {
        "question": "単独",
        "answer": "たんどく"
    },
    {
        "question": "細菌",
        "answer": "さいきん"
    },
    {
        "question": "擦れ違い",
        "answer": "すれちがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "突如",
        "answer": "とつじょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "効率",
        "answer": "こうりつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "兵器",
        "answer": "へいき"
    },
    {
        "question": "横綱",
        "answer": "よこづな"
    },
    {
        "question": "便宜",
        "answer": "べんぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "擦れる",
        "answer": "すれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "階級",
        "answer": "かいきゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "其れ故",
        "answer": "それゆえ"
    },
    {
        "question": "吃驚",
        "answer": "びっくり"
    },
    {
        "question": "形態",
        "answer": "けいたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "賜る",
        "answer": "たまわる"
    },
    {
        "question": "ご無沙汰",
        "answer": "ごぶさた"
    },
    {
        "question": "基",
        "answer": "もとい"
    },
    {
        "question": "製法",
        "answer": "せいほう"
    },
    {
        "question": "顧みる",
        "answer": "かえりみる"
    },
    {
        "question": "侵略",
        "answer": "しんりゃく"
    },
    {
        "question": "異性",
        "answer": "いせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "如何",
        "answer": "いかが"
    },
    {
        "question": "態勢",
        "answer": "たいせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "促進",
        "answer": "そくしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "傍ら",
        "answer": "かたわら"
    },
    {
        "question": "閲覧",
        "answer": "えつらん"
    },
    {
        "question": "瞬き",
        "answer": "またたき"
    },
    {
        "question": "降伏",
        "answer": "こうふく"
    },
    {
        "question": "縮まる",
        "answer": "ちぢまる"
    },
    {
        "question": "催す",
        "answer": "もよおす"
    },
    {
        "question": "素っ気ない",
        "answer": "そっけない"
    },
    {
        "question": "復興",
        "answer": "ふっこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "宜しく",
        "answer": "よろしく"
    },
    {
        "question": "起源",
        "answer": "きげん"
    },
    {
        "question": "掲げる",
        "answer": "かかげる"
    },
    {
        "question": "織る",
        "answer": "おる"
    },
    {
        "question": "強烈",
        "answer": "きょうれつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "距離",
        "answer": "きょり"
    },
    {
        "question": "尻尾",
        "answer": "しっぽ"
    },
    {
        "question": "沿い",
        "answer": "ぞい"
    },
    {
        "question": "粗筋",
        "answer": "あらすじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "高尚",
        "answer": "こうしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "反応",
        "answer": "はんのう"
    },
    {
        "question": "電源",
        "answer": "でんげん"
    },
    {
        "question": "紛らわしい",
        "answer": "まぎらわしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "嵩張る",
        "answer": "かさばる"
    },
    {
        "question": "冠",
        "answer": "かん"
    },
    {
        "question": "堪らない",
        "answer": "たまらない"
    },
    {
        "question": "雪崩",
        "answer": "なだれ"
    },
    {
        "question": "中枢",
        "answer": "ちゅうすう"
    },
    {
        "question": "取り締まり",
        "answer": "とりしまり"
    },
    {
        "question": "偏る",
        "answer": "かたよる"
    },
    {
        "question": "軍艦",
        "answer": "ぐんかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "遺跡",
        "answer": "いせき"
    },
    {
        "question": "吹奏",
        "answer": "すいそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "宝器",
        "answer": "ほうき"
    },
    {
        "question": "釣鐘",
        "answer": "つりがね"
    },
    {
        "question": "滑稽",
        "answer": "こっけい"
    },
    {
        "question": "趣旨",
        "answer": "しゅし"
    },
    {
        "question": "挑む",
        "answer": "いどむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "盾",
        "answer": "たて"
    },
    {
        "question": "半端",
        "answer": "はんぱ"
    },
    {
        "question": "殊に",
        "answer": "ことに"
    },
    {
        "question": "倣",
        "answer": "ほう"
    },
    {
        "question": "厳密",
        "answer": "げんみつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "脚色",
        "answer": "きゃくしょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "抽選",
        "answer": "ちゅうせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "保育",
        "answer": "ほいく"
    },
    {
        "question": "沢山",
        "answer": "たくさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "委託",
        "answer": "いたく"
    },
    {
        "question": "策",
        "answer": "さく"
    },
    {
        "question": "吐く",
        "answer": "つく"
    },
    {
        "question": "旦那",
        "answer": "だんな"
    },
    {
        "question": "怠慢",
        "answer": "たいまん"
    },
    {
        "question": "診療",
        "answer": "しんりょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "潜入",
        "answer": "せんにゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "付属",
        "answer": "ふぞく"
    },
    {
        "question": "殴る",
        "answer": "なぐる"
    },
    {
        "question": "謝絶",
        "answer": "しゃぜつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "素朴",
        "answer": "そぼく"
    },
    {
        "question": "雄",
        "answer": "おす"
    },
    {
        "question": "織",
        "answer": "おり"
    },
    {
        "question": "補償",
        "answer": "ほしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "模索",
        "answer": "もさく"
    },
    {
        "question": "艶",
        "answer": "えん"
    },
    {
        "question": "伴う",
        "answer": "ともなう"
    },
    {
        "question": "凡そ",
        "answer": "およそ"
    },
    {
        "question": "棟",
        "answer": "とう"
    },
    {
        "question": "反射",
        "answer": "はんしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "整然",
        "answer": "せいぜん"
    },
    {
        "question": "伐",
        "answer": "ばつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "勧誘",
        "answer": "かんゆう"
    },
    {
        "question": "実践",
        "answer": "じっせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "兼用",
        "answer": "けんよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "貫く",
        "answer": "つらぬく"
    },
    {
        "question": "束縛",
        "answer": "そくばく"
    },
    {
        "question": "嵩む",
        "answer": "かさむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "配慮",
        "answer": "はいりょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "郷愁",
        "answer": "きょうしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "宙返り",
        "answer": "ちゅうがえり"
    },
    {
        "question": "溝",
        "answer": "こう"
    },
    {
        "question": "戸締り",
        "answer": "とじまり"
    },
    {
        "question": "執着",
        "answer": "しゅうじゃく"
    },
    {
        "question": "裸足",
        "answer": "はだし"
    },
    {
        "question": "忠実",
        "answer": "ちゅうじつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "点検",
        "answer": "てんけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "官僚",
        "answer": "かんりょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "印鑑",
        "answer": "いんかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "干渉",
        "answer": "かんしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "月賦",
        "answer": "げっぷ"
    },
    {
        "question": "密集",
        "answer": "みっしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "控室",
        "answer": "ひかえしつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "魂",
        "answer": "こん"
    },
    {
        "question": "雅致",
        "answer": "がち"
    },
    {
        "question": "天皇",
        "answer": "すめらぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "討議",
        "answer": "とうぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "磁気",
        "answer": "じき"
    },
    {
        "question": "抑制",
        "answer": "よくせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "傾斜",
        "answer": "けいしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "渋い",
        "answer": "しぶい"
    },
    {
        "question": "一挙に",
        "answer": "いっきょに"
    },
    {
        "question": "基金",
        "answer": "ききん"
    },
    {
        "question": "浜辺",
        "answer": "はまべ"
    },
    {
        "question": "沿線",
        "answer": "えんせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "自我",
        "answer": "じが"
    },
    {
        "question": "洪水",
        "answer": "こうずい"
    },
    {
        "question": "堪える",
        "answer": "こたえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "お宮",
        "answer": "おみや"
    },
    {
        "question": "派",
        "answer": "は"
    },
    {
        "question": "購入",
        "answer": "こうにゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "介護",
        "answer": "かいご"
    },
    {
        "question": "態々",
        "answer": "わざわざ"
    },
    {
        "question": "正義",
        "answer": "せいぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "樹木",
        "answer": "じゅもく"
    },
    {
        "question": "有益",
        "answer": "ゆうえき"
    },
    {
        "question": "穂",
        "answer": "ほ"
    },
    {
        "question": "酸化",
        "answer": "さんか"
    },
    {
        "question": "稲光",
        "answer": "いなびかり"
    },
    {
        "question": "精巧",
        "answer": "せいこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "奉る",
        "answer": "たてまつる"
    },
    {
        "question": "保温",
        "answer": "ほおん"
    },
    {
        "question": "貴女",
        "answer": "あなた"
    },
    {
        "question": "染みる",
        "answer": "しみる"
    },
    {
        "question": "放射能",
        "answer": "ほうしゃのう"
    },
    {
        "question": "災害",
        "answer": "さいがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "叶う",
        "answer": "かなう"
    },
    {
        "question": "人柄",
        "answer": "ひとがら"
    },
    {
        "question": "素早い",
        "answer": "すばやい"
    },
    {
        "question": "緩和",
        "answer": "かんわ"
    },
    {
        "question": "把握",
        "answer": "はあく"
    },
    {
        "question": "佳句",
        "answer": "かく"
    },
    {
        "question": "従業員",
        "answer": "じゅうぎょういん"
    },
    {
        "question": "敵",
        "answer": "かたき"
    },
    {
        "question": "乏しい",
        "answer": "とぼしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "箇所",
        "answer": "かしょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "浪費",
        "answer": "ろうひ"
    },
    {
        "question": "類推",
        "answer": "るいすい"
    },
    {
        "question": "揺らぐ",
        "answer": "ゆらぐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "焦る",
        "answer": "あせる"
    },
    {
        "question": "削減",
        "answer": "さくげん"
    },
    {
        "question": "弓",
        "answer": "ゆみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "斜面",
        "answer": "しゃめん"
    },
    {
        "question": "一筋",
        "answer": "ひとすき"
    },
    {
        "question": "補充",
        "answer": "ほじゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "碑",
        "answer": "いしぶみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "施す",
        "answer": "ほどこす"
    },
    {
        "question": "修了",
        "answer": "しゅうりょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "概略",
        "answer": "がいりゃく"
    },
    {
        "question": "圏",
        "answer": "けん"
    },
    {
        "question": "下痢",
        "answer": "げり"
    },
    {
        "question": "無駄遣い",
        "answer": "むだづかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "応急",
        "answer": "おうきゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "養護",
        "answer": "ようご"
    },
    {
        "question": "桐",
        "answer": "きり"
    },
    {
        "question": "凝る",
        "answer": "こごる"
    },
    {
        "question": "遥か",
        "answer": "はるか"
    },
    {
        "question": "滅茶苦茶",
        "answer": "めちゃくちゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "施行",
        "answer": "しぎょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "沼",
        "answer": "ぬま"
    },
    {
        "question": "同志",
        "answer": "どうし"
    }
]